Vinayak Das

Student

Punjabi Bagh West New Delhi, 110026

Email ID: vinayakd909@gmail.com Phone Number: +91 7742522488

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/phenyloder

Languages Known: English, Hindi

GitHub Profile: https://github.com/phenyloder

A highly motivated and enthusiastic student who is always ready to learn new things. Interested in sports and coding and aims to develop and work on projects in human mankind. Have experience in managing groups and maintaining a balance between duties and rights.

SKILLS

- Team Work
- Web Development (HTML, CSS, JS, ReactJS, NodeJS, Django, Bootstrap)
- Cloud Computing (Certified course by IBM with edX: https://bit.ly/edX_Cloud)
- Computer Skills (Google Forms, MS Office)
- Coding With C and C++ (Certified By Udemy: https://bit.ly/udemy_c), 2 Star on CodeChef
- Technical Writing
- Planning And Coordination

EXPERIENCE

Google Developer Students Club, NIT Silchar - Junior Member (Web Module)

August 2021 - Present

- Learned GIT and GitHub.
- Made Projects To-Do List, GDSC Explore, Srijan 3.0 Website
- Participated In Session: Introduction To Cloud Computing.
- Working In the Editorial team and writing many contents and Invitations.

GyanSagar, NIT Silchar - Senior Member

January 2021 - Present

- Working as the lead of the Publicity Poster module
- Organised Write-Up competition on the occasion of Durga Puja
- Working As Script Writer For Karmaveer.
- Working As Educator In Gyan Online Team. (Taught students of class 9th and 10th)

Instrumentation and Electronics Engineering Society, NITS - Executive Member

May 2021 - Present

- Organised INSEES Invictus Episodes 1 and 2.
- Reached out various guests and passed out seniors to invite in INSEES Invictus
- Wrote content for Facebook posts and INSEES Annual Magazine.
- Managed Placing Orders, Making Forms and Excel sheets for Branch Outfits.

Other Experiences -

December, 2020 - Present

- Worked in marketing team in SRIJAN 2.0
- Worked in content writing team in Mechatrix 8.0 (Annual Fest Of Mechanical Society)
- Organised Mecha Royale for Mechanical Branch with Series Of Events.

EDUCATION

National Institute Of Technology Silchar, Assam - B.Tech

Branch: Electronics And Instrumentation Engineering

December 2020 - Present (Graduation Ends in 2024)

Current CGPA: 9.4

• MS Memorial Academy, Patna, Bihar - Student

March 2019 - March 2020

CBSE 12th Board: Secured 94.4%

PROJECTS COMPLETED

- 1. Working on Srijan 3.0 Website (ECell NIT Silchar's Annual Fest for encouraging Entrepreneurship) Made using EJS, NodeJS and MongoDB
- 2. Made Gyansagar Conclave Website using HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap:

Link to Website: https://gyansagar-conclave.herokuapp.com/

3. Contributed to GDSC Explore Website - Made using NextJS and TailwindCSS

Link To Website: https://gdscexplore.live

- 4. Participated in Script Winter Of Code 2.0 and contributed to various Open Source projects like Blood Buddy, Dezenix etc.
- 5. Made To-Do List Project Using HTML, CSS, JS under GDSC NIT Silchar

Link To Website: https://to-do-list-vinayakd909.netlify.app/

6. Made Project0: Search using HTML CSS and JS

Link To Website: https://phenyloder.github.io